<Document>
  # NT New Frontiers Program

Thank you for signing up for the New Frontiers Program! As a Nanotrasen employee, you're helping to develop the furthest reaches of space!

[color=#33bbff]If you'd like a hand, ask on the radio, or talk to somebody.[/color]
The [color=#dd0000]Valet[/color] or [color=#009933]Station Representative[/color] should be able to help, they're to the right of medbay.

## Economy
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerBankATM"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SpaceCash1000"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerShipyard"/>
  </Box>
  Any money that you make is [bold]yours[/bold], and will be available in future shifts if deposited at a [color=#44cc00]Galactic Bank ATM[/color] on Frontier Outpost or Tinnia's Rest.

To make money, why not:
- Join a ship's crew? Ask on the radio if anyone needs extra crew, and work to help your captain.
- Get a job on station? Ask the [color=#009933]Station Representative[/color] (follow the SR signs) if anything needs doing.
- Use a [color=#cccc00]shipyard console[/color] to purchase your own ship?

## Amenities
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineAstroVend"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="VendingMachineAmmo"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MachineCryoSleepPod"/>
  </Box>
  Some provisions (e.g. air tanks, salvage equipment) are available from vendors on Frontier Outpost, but most amenities (medical services, food) should be offered by players on shuttles or at the Trade Depot.

Be sure to stock up at the Trade Depot if going out on an extended voyage, and take advantage of the [color=#33bbff]medical insurance tracker[/color] in your loadout, or from the NanoMed vendor in medbay.

<!-- Coyote and Aurora's Song start -->

Shifts in the Sector can last for anywhere from [color=#33bbff]six[/color] to [color=#33bbff]seventy-two[/color] hours.
If you need to end your shift early or take a break, use the [color=#33bbff]cryo sleep chambers[/color] in the clinic on the central station.

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PottedPlant0"/>
  </Box>

  Fun fact: Sleeping in your ship overnight can make you suffer from CO2 buildup. This is usually due to the power in your ship dying, which leads to your scrubber dying, which leads to you dying too.

  What can you do about this?

  Two options: bolt your doors open to let the CO2 diffuse over a larger area, OR use a potted plant! Potted plants can scrub the CO2 out of the air, slowly, but more than fast enough to keep you alive overnight.

  To make a plant scrub the air, simply wrench it to the ground by your bed. It'll do the rest! You might expect it to make oxygen, but it doesn't. It just removes CO2.

  This works with any potted plant with the Label on it (you'll know it when you see it), even if its a plastic plant or something that wouldn't really make sense to process CO2. Generally, if its even vaguely potted plant like, it'll work. Unless it doesn't.

<!-- Coyote and Aurora's Song end -->
</Document>
